Evan Bruno

evanbruno22@gmail.com | (925)-490-8022 | Martinez, California | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/evan-bruno-11bb8222/

| GitHub: https://github.com/evanbruno617 | eBay: https://ebay.com/usr/evabrun0

Summary

My experience in the retail industry has allowed me to develop strong organizational, teamwork, multitasking, and customer service skills in order to work efficiently in a fast paced environment. Developing skills such as product research and inventory management was necessary to grow my ecommerce business allowing me to increase my sales tenfold from when I first started. Currently attending a data analytics bootcamp at UC Berkeley Extension where I am pursuing my interest in data science to become a data analyst.

Professional Experience

Crate & Barrel 08/2021- Present Day

Stock Associate

Walnut Creek, California

 Recognized by manager for swiftly completing organizational tasks of the stockroom and online orders with more than 50 a day.

Ecommerce Business Owner

07/2019 - Present Day

• Prepared weekly sales report to analyze how products were performing and increased inventory for more successful items which lead to a 200% revenue growth in 2020.

Projects

Stock Analysis | https://github.com/evanbruno617/Stock-Ticker-Analysis

- Analyzing various stocks and charting their historical data using a TD Ameritrade api key and Mpl Finance to chart the given data.
- This project allows the user to analyze stock charts and trends in price action.

Mission To Mars | https://github.com/evanbruno617/Mission to Mars

- The purpose of this project is to scrape data consisting of current news regarding Mars.
- Navigated the website to gather necessary images and articles using splinter and BeautifulSoup. With this information I created a web application using HTML and CSS.

Technical Skills

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

Backend: MySQL, MongoDB, Python

Education

UC Berkeley Extension, Online Data Analytics Certificate

01/2022 - 07/2022